themill.com 2014-06-29

# Privacy Policy - The Mill

This website is open to the public and has been established by The Mill in order that clients and other interested persons can learn more about The Mill. Anyone can visit this site anonymously to find out about The Mill's services. The Mill is committed to safeguarding the privacy of visitors to this site. The following policy explains what personal information we may collect and how such information will be treated. Should this policy change at any time a notice to that effect will be displayed on the home page.

This policy covers all the websites operated by The Mill. Please keep in mind that not all the services covered are available from every site. The extent and nature of the personal information collected in relation to each site will differ and this policy will apply accordingly.

**1\. Cookies**

1.1. A cookie is a small amount of information which is stored by your web browser on your computer's hard drive when you access the website.  
1.2. The cookies store and track information concerning your use of the website such as the pages accessed and the date and time of such access. The information is collected in the name of your internet service provider.  
1.3. This information is collected to enable The Mill to generate statistics and measure site activity. The Mill uses the information to improve the effectiveness of your visit to the website and where appropriate to deliver to you a better and more personalised service.  
1.4. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies but you can usually change your browser to prevent this. You may not be able to use all the features on some of The Mill's websites if your browser does not accept cookies or if you have altered your web browser accordingly.

**2\. Personal Information collected by The Mill**

2.1. During normal use of the website The Mill does not collect personal information about you.  
2.2. Where you are required to register for a particular service The Mill will collect adequate and relevant personal information necessary for performing that service.  
2.3. Where The Mill collects personal information a link will be provided to this policy and you will be required to confirm that you have read it before access to the appropriate service will be granted.

**3\. How The Mill uses the Information**

3.1. The Mill's primary purpose for collecting personal information is to fulfil your service requirements.  
3.2. The Mill is committed to improving its websites and online services and may use the information collected from visitors to achieve this.

**4\. Information Sharing**

4.1. The Mill does not sell trade or rent your personal information to others. The Mill does not subject to paragraphs 4.2 and 4.3 below provide your personal information to any third party save where it is required to do so by law.  
4.2. Where a particular service is provided in conjunction with a third party The Mill will need to share your personal information with that third party. Your personal information will be provided solely for the purpose of providing the relevant service. This will be made clear when you register for the service.  
4.3. The Mill will not in any event share your personal information with any third party without your express consent to do so.  
4.4. The Mill may provide to third parties aggregate statistics concerning the use of the website. Such information will include no personally identifying information.

**5\. Your choices concerning the use of you Personal Information**

5.1. You may at any time request that The Mill delete all your personal information held in relation to any service. This will result in you not being able to use the relevant service. You may at any time re-register with any service.  
5.2. You may request from The Mill details of all your personal information collected and stored by The Mill. The Mill is entitled to charge a reasonable fee for providing such details.  
5.3. Should your personal information change at any time you may inform The Mill and request that your personal information in updated.

**6\. Consent**

6.1. By using the website(s) you consent to the collection and use of your personal information for the purposed specified.  
6.2. You will be required to indicate your express consent where The Mill may share your personal information with third parties outside the European Economic Area or where you are providing 'sensitive' information. In all such cases this will be made clear.

**7\. Privacy**

7.1. The Mill is committed to maintaining your privacy.  
7.2. Whenever The Mill collects and stores personal information it takes steps to ensure that the personal information is treated securely in accordance with this policy. The Mill cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information which you transmit to The Mill and you do so at your own risk. Once The Mill receives your transmission it makes its best efforts to ensure its security on its systems.

**8\. Authorisation**

8.1. The Mill (Facility) Limited is an authorised data controller for the purposes of the Data Protection Act 1998 (registration number Z5439074). Details are available at www.dpr.gov.uk.

If you need to contact us in relation to this policy please do so by email to itsystems@mill.co.uk or by post to The Mill (Facility) Limited 40-41 Great Marlborough Street, London W1F 7JQ marking your correspondence "Privacy Policy".
